# **Adam Florence Software Engineer**

**Address:** Newtown, NSW, Australia

**Phone:** (+61) 0414 088 636

 Email:
 aflorence999@gmail.com

 LinkedIn:
 linkedin.com/in/adam-florence

 GitHub:
 github.com/iamadamsrepository

#### **PROFILE**

Junior Software Engineer at Akuna Capital, an international options trading firm. Specializing in Python development within the risk division. Designing, implementing, and maintaining applications and reports for risk assessment and while simultaneously being a live support-first role. Bachelor of Computer Engineering (Honours) from the University of New South Wales, graduated in 2021. Experienced in software development and deep learning, honed through honours thesis research on resource efficiency in deep neural networks.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Python - AdvancedDart - IntermediateHaskell - BasicC - IntermediateSwift - BasicJavascript - BasicC++ - IntermediateCUDA - BasicJava - Basic

## **TECHNOLOGIES**

Grafana - AdvancedAsyncio - AdvancedFlutter - IntermediatePostgresSQL - AdvancedFastAPI - AdvancedAWS - Intermediate

Pytorch - Advanced Python Django - Intermediate Kubernetes - Intermediate

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Akuna Capital - Junior Software Engineer**

Jan 2022 - Present

- The most experienced developer in my small risk team.
- Responsible for leading live-support of our applications.
- Designed, implemented and maintained applications and automated reports.
- Gained domain-specific knowledge in finance and options trading.

# Cyberdweller Technologies - Software Developer and IT Assistant

Jul 2019 - Jun 2021

- Developed an app for a client using Python Django and Flutter.
- Wrote automation scripts for client's machines in Powershell.

## Kleemann Elevators Australia - Prospector

Jan 2018 - Jul 2019

- Ran prospecting, opportunity development, for the Australian branch of Kleemann Elevators.
- Responsible for communicating with construction companies' contracts administrators, as well as managing the company's opportunities database.

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Resource Efficient Deep Neural Networks For Nanosatellites**

- Honours thesis project studying and testing the latest techniques used for reducing the energy cost of CNNs for image classification and filtering. All with the purpose of making them viable on edge hardware in nanosatellites.
- Implemented and quantitatively evaluated these techniques individually and in combination using Pytorch with a YOLO-style image classifier.

#### Writersblok Flutter App

A Flutter application designed to help musicians find some inspiration and curb their writer's block.

## **Broadcastr Blockchain App for COMP6452 at UNSW**

 An ethereum based application, written in Solidity and Javascript, enabling a user to broadcast information in a way that is immutable and authenticated.

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Engineering (Honours) - University of New South Wales - 2016 - 2021